<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
  xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
  xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
  xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
  xmlns:trackback="http://madskills.com/public/xml/rss/module/trackback/">
  <channel>
    <title>Between Bastion and Buttress</title>
    <link>https://blog.such.computer</link>
    <description>Code, Cloud Computing, Community and Common Sense</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
    <item>
      <title>For The Joy And Pain Of It</title>
      <link>https://blog.such.computer/posts/for-the-pain-of-it</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This year has been rather strange for me, thus far. Some things have gone right, some things wrong and a lot of in-between. It has also been a period of reflection and deep introspection.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <dc:date>2015-01-14T00:00:00-05:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Your First Telescope Should Be A Pair Of Binoculars</title>
      <link>https://blog.such.computer/posts/your-first-telescope</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Very few things captivate the curiosity and imagination of children and adults like outer space. In awe we look up the sky searching for galaxies, planets, satellites, comets, shooting stars and many other space objects. So, when that insatiable curiosity reaches the limits of the human eye, many of us begin our search for tools to satiate that yearning. Telescopes have been the go-to solution for the aspiring astronomer and space enthusiast. However, here I will make the case that your first telescope should not be a telescope at all, but, rather, a good pair of binoculars.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2014 12:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <dc:date>2014-12-31T12:30:00-05:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Checking for and Setting Up Forward Secrecy</title>
      <link>https://blog.such.computer/posts/checking-and-setting-web-and-ssh-forward-secrecy</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I would like to preface this post by making it abundantly clear that I’m neither a InfoSec expert nor a “hacker” of any sort. If anything, I’m not particularly well versed on this subject, so I’m posting this for both my own edification and sharing the knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2014 20:45:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <dc:date>2014-12-28T20:45:00-05:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>On Distance Running</title>
      <link>https://blog.such.computer/posts/on-distance-running</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a post I’ve been meaning to write for a while, but never got around to it. Last night I came across the following quote by David Goggins that re-kindled my inspiration to write it:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;Running is running. It hurts, but that’s all it does. The most difficult part of the training is training your mind. You build calluses on your feet to endure the road. You build calluses on your mind to endure the pain. There’s only one way to do that. You have to get out there and run.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 10:45:00 -0500</pubDate>
      <dc:date>2014-12-10T10:45:00-05:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When you run a marathon, what do you think about?</title>
      <link>https://blog.such.computer/posts/When-you-run-a-marathon</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;So, this is a question that is often asked of people when they run marathons: “What do you think about while you’re in the race?” Below is a semi-stream-of-thought what I think about in a race:&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2014 22:45:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <dc:date>2014-10-08T22:45:00-04:00</dc:date>
    </item>
    <dc:date>2015-01-14T00:00:00-05:00</dc:date>
  </channel>
</rss>